virtualspirits.com 2018-06-24

# Privacy

Privacy policy

The use of vSpirits Technologies ltd. ("Virtual Spirits") website(s), software (“Software”) and services (“Services”) provided by Virtual Spirits on virtualspirits.com and virtualspirits.eu platforms are subject to the hereunder provisions of this Privacy Policy. 

**1\. General**

Virtual Spirits takes your privacy seriously. We gather certain types of information about our users and we want to help you understand the terms related to the collection and use of the information, which we collect. This Privacy Policy discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and what choices you have regarding the collection of such information. 

BY USING OR ACCESSING ANY VIRTUAL SPIRITS WEBSITE OR USING THE PRODUCT, YOU AGREE TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS HEREUNDER DESCRIBED), ALL IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET HEREUNDER. VIRTUAL SPIRITS MAY AMEND THIS POLICY FROM TIME TO TIME. A NOTIFICATION OF ANY SUCH AMENDMENT SHALL BE POSTED ON: <https://www.virtualspirits.com/privacy.aspx>

**2\. Collection of Information from VirtualSpirits customers**

We collect personal information when you sign up for our Services, when you access our Services or otherwise provide us with the information. 

We collect personal information when you visit the VirtualSpirits websites, use Services offered on our websites or engage with us either by email, web form, instant message, phone, or post content on our websites (including forums and blogs). We also collect any additional information that you might provide to us. 

Use of certain features of the Product may require submission of certain personal information, including your first and last name, email address, payment details, a nick name (user ID) and a password, as well as information such as IP address, the device and browser you use. 

Virtual Spirits may also collect or receive additional non personally identifiable usage information specifically related to the use of a particular feature or offering on the Virtual Spirits Product or website(s). 

Virtual Spirits may also collect or receive (in some cases as part of the internet communication protocol) certain non personally identifiable technical information, when the Virtual Spirits website(s) and pages are visited or when the Virtual Spirits Product is used. 

We may share such information with third party partners or agents involved in delivering the services you're purchasing from VirtualSpirits 

To process your information as described above, we rely on the following legal bases: 

Performance of agreement: the use of your information may be necessary to perform the agreement that you have with us. For example, if you use our services, we will use your information to carry out our obligation to complete and administer that service under the agreement that we have with you 

Legitimate interests: the processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us, namely for information security. We also want to provide you with the best suitable content of the website, emails and newsletter, to improve and promote our products and services, and for administrative, fraud detection and legal purposes 

Consent: we may rely on your consent to use your Personal Data for certain direct marketing purposes 

**3\. Collection of Information from VirtualSpirits customers' customers**

We collect chat transcripts between our customers (businesses) and their customers, for the purpose of showing reports to those businesses. We collect chat transcripts between our customers’ customers (customers, prospects,support users, visitors) and our customers' chatbots or live agents. The chat transcripts may include personal information you and they provide during the chat such as name, email, phone number, information about products or orders, information about support inquiries, IP address, and information about the device and browser you use. 

We collect this information when you use or access our chat software on a website, instant messaging, or mobile app that uses our Services, such as when you visit a merchant site and have a chat conversation to get answers or support. 

We use this information to provide our customers with the Services, including chatbot software for automatic chat and live chat to provide answers and support. We share this information and chat transcripts with our customers as part of the Services. We also use this information to improve our Services. 

We use some of the personal information you provide us to conduct some level of automated decision-making -- for example, we use certain personal information (for example, ip addresses) to automatically block certain potentially spam chat conversations transactions for a short period of time. 

We may also share your information to conform to legal requirements, or to respond to lawful court orders, subpoenas, warrants, or other requests by public authorities (including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements). 

**4\. International Transfer Of Information Collected**

For software and services on virtualspirits.com we store personal information on servers in Data centers within the United States; to facilitate our global operations, we may access such information from around the world, including from other countries in which Virtual Spirits has operations. 

For software and services on virtualspirits.eu we store personal information on servers in Data centers within the European Union; to facilitate our EU operations, we may access such information from countries in which Virtual Spirits has operations within the European Union, European Economic Area, and from Israel. 

**5\. Data disclosure**

We do not sell your personal data to third parties. 

The information is used to operate and improve the features, offerings and content presented to you by Virtual Spirits, to personalize the content provided to you; to fulfill your requests for products, programs, and services; to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries; to conduct research about your use of the Product and/or website(s), email communication, website(s) and pages; and to help offer you other products, programs, or services that may be of interest. 

Notwithstanding the foregoing, your information may be accessed and disclosed if and as required by legal procedures such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, or if it is necessary for VirtualSpirits security and its rights protection, including the protection against the claims submitted by the third parties. 

**6\. Cookies**

Virtual Spirits may use cookies or similar technologies to enhance and personalize your experience of the Product and/or of Virtual Spirits web sites, including to operate and improve offerings through the Product and/or web sites; to help authenticate your identity when you visit and transact with the Product, and/or web sites; to remember your preferences and registration information; to present and help measure and research the effectiveness of the various offerings, and e-mail communications (by determining which e-mails you open and act upon). 

Additionally, Virtual Spirits or its advertisers may use other companies known as third party ad servers to help present advertisements online in connection with the Product, and/or web sites. These third party ad servers may use cookies or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies, not Virtual Spirits. 

Virtual Spirits does not require that you accept cookies, and you may disable cookies at any time. However, some functionality of our Products and/or web sites may be impaired if you decline to accept cookies. 

**7\. Data protection**

Virtual Spirits applies technical safety measures of the highest standards to protect the provided data against loss, destruction, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal data submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. 

Virtual Spirits takes all necessary steps to update and modernize data protection system. When you access the product's control panel and when visitors use our product on https secured websites, we automatically encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer (SSL) and Transport Layer Security (TLS) protocols. 

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

**8\. Special Note for Parents**

You must be 18 years or older or at least the age of majority in the jurisdiction where you reside or from which you use this Service. 

**9\. Third Parties' Practices.**

This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices exercised by other providers of products or services, advertisers or other web sites, or companies/people that Virtual Spirits does not own or control, or does not employ or manage. 

**10\. Residents of the European Economic Area (“EEA”)**

Virtual Spirits works with businesses and users around the world, including in the EEA. 

If: (a) you are established in the European Economic Area (EEA); (b) you provide goods or services to customers in the EEA; or (c) you are otherwise subject to the requirements of the EU General Data Protection Regulation, Virtual Spirits collection, processing and use of personal information of any European residents is also subject to our Data Processing Addendum here <https://www.virtualspirits.com/dpa.aspx>

If you or your customers are located in Europe you are required to use Virtual Spirits software and services hosted at virtualspirits.eu. If you or your customers are located in Europe you should not use our software and services hosted at virtualspirits.com 

If you are located in the EEA, you have certain rights under European law with respect to your personal data, including the right to request access to, correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your personal data. If you are a customer or a visitor of VirtualSpirits websites, or a user of VirtualSpirits support services and wish to exercise these rights, please reach out to us using the contact information below. If you are a business visitor or merchants customer and wish to exercise these rights, please contact the business merchants you interacted with directly -- we serve as a processor on their behalf, and can only forward your request to them to allow them to respond. 

Additionally, if you are located in the EEA, we note that we are generally processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above, unless we are required by law to obtain your consent for a particular processing operation. 

**10\. Modification and Deletion of Personally Identifiable Information**

VirtualSpirits understands that you have rights over your personal information, and takes reasonable steps to allow you to access, correct, amend, delete, port, or limit the use of your personal information. If you are a customer, you can update many types of personal information, such as contact information, directly within your account settings. If you are unable to change your personal information within your account settings, or if you are concerned about data collected as you visit VirtualSpirits’s websites or use our support services, please contact us to make the required changes. If you are a visitor and wish to exercise these rights, please contact the business or merchants you interacted with directly -- we serve as a processor on their behalf, and can only forward your request to them to allow them to respond. It’s important to remember that if you delete or limit the use of your personal information, the Services may not function properly. 

If you have any questions about your personal information or this policy, or if you would like to make a complaint about how VirtualSpirits processes your personal data, please contact VirtualSpirits by email at support@virtualspirits.com 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 14, 2018.
